

# **PROFILE**

I offer 3.5 years of professional experience in development on mostly.

Currently, I am working as a Software Engineer in Coventry UK for Sainsbury's.

My goal is to keep learning and growing my career as a Full-Stack Software Engineer.

Programming is my passion, I am highly motivated, focused, with a lot of will to keep learning.

# **CONTACT**

Phone:

+44 7448719858

Email:

atanasskambitovv@gmail.com

# **LANGUAGES**

English | Italian | Spanish | Bulgarian

### **HOBBIES & SPORTS**

Badminton | Football | Chess

# LINKS

GitHub:

https://github.com/NASOKILA

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/atanaskambitov-a69528162/

# ATANAS KAMBITOV

# Software Engineer

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Sainsbury's | Software Engineer | Coventry UK 03/12/2018 - Now

Experienced with Full-Stack development including Cloud technologies, Unit and Integration testing.

Hands on experience in Responsive Web Design with ReactJS, React Hooks, Redux, Angular 2+, Javascript, Typescript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Jest & Enzyme, Karma, HTML5 & CSS3, LESS & SASS, .Net Core, NUnit, XUnit, SQL, Mongo DB. Also Azure, Azure DevOps, Docker, MVC, MVVM, REST, SOAP XML, JSON, YAML, Git, GitHub and more.

Usage of PowerBI for reporting and Datadog for alerting and monitoring. Working in an agile way with scrum in a team of five people providing code quality, latency, stability and performance following solid principles.

SoftUni | Software Engineer | Sofia, Bulgaria 05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 years)

Hands on experience with backend API's, databases and frontend apps with ReactJS and Angular 2+ JQuery and NodeJS + ExpressJS.

Quickly deliver quality code and meet deadlines on multiple projects with deferent technologies, languages and frameworks.

# **SKILLS**

Agile | Scrum | Microservice Architecture | Azure | Solid Principles | MVC MVVM | Kubernetes | GitHub | Docker | REST API | .NET Core | .Net Framework React.js | Redux | SQL | Angular | Typescript | JavaScript | Mongo DB | JQuery HTML5 & CSS3 | Less & Sass | Bootstrap | Node.js & Express.js

### **EDUCATION**

# South-West University "Neofit Rilski"

15/09/2014 - 25/05/2018 (4 years) Bachelor degree in Informatics.

### Private Software University (SoftUni)

05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 years)

Professionally graduated and qualified C# and JavaScript developer.

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

.Net Core + ReactJS

https://github.com/NASOKILA/todolist.backendhttps://github.com/NASOKILA/todolist.frontendhttps://github.com/NASOKILA/todolist.frontendhttps://github.com/NASOKILA/todolist.frontendhttps://github.com/NASOKILA/todolist.backendhttps://github.com/

#### **Angular**

https://nasokila.github.io/comix-shop/

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/comix-shop

#### ReactJS

https://nasokila.github.io/house-shop/

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/house-shop